<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Concetto</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Concetto</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="spardha_desc">Compromising of 3 members each there will be approximately 15-20 Groups (Depending on the participants). The quiz will be Divided into 3 Rounds. \n
•	First Round Would Consist of the questions Regarding the CEO, Higher management authorities, technology based and Company related questions where each team will be given a set of questions that they have to answer, Top 10 teams would be selected for next round. \n
•	Round 2 will be conducted with the Help of Projector where Pictures will be displayed on the screen and the participants would be required to guess the right answer. \n
•	Third Round Would Consist of questions related to Latest Business changes and technical innovations. \n
    </string>

    <string name="spardha_rules">Round 1-There will be 25-30 questions and time allotted will be approximately 30 minutes. Group members would discuss and mark the answer correctly. No Negative Marking. \n
Round 2- The Team Would Nominate 1 Member From The Group. The Logo/Symbols/Pictures would be Displayed and the member will have to guess the correct answer, time given would be 10 seconds each, team will Lose marks if the member Fails to answer. 2-3 such rounds will be conducted. Top 5 teams would go to the next round. \n
Round 3- Current Business and technological questions would be asked Individually to members of the teams for which 15 seconds will be provided. Each member of the team would get 1 question, and 1 bonus question for 1 team of 5 marks to make up. \n
In case of tie, tie breaker question would be asked. \n
    </string>

    <string name="spardha_contact">A) Deepti
     Contact No. 7783024700 \n
        B) Krishna Sudhakar Sonvane
     Contact No. 9158464845 \n
    </string>

    <string name="spardha_time">2 hours</string>


    <string name="electrabuzz_desc">ITS A KNOWLEDGE HUNT. THE EVENT IS ALL ABOUT TESTING THE BASIC ELECTRONICS YOU COME ACROSS IN YOUR REAL DAY TO DAY LIFE. IT COMPRISES OF THREE ROUNDS OF POSSIBLE ELIMINATIONS. \n
ROUND 1:  A TEAM IS FORMED AND QUESTIONS RELATED TO ELECTRONIC COMPONENT IS GIVEN. THEY HAVE TO SEARCH FOR THE COMPONENT AND DROP IT IN TEAM’S DROP BOX.. EACH CORRECT COMPONENT(ANSWER) WILL BE A CLUE TO THE NEXT QUESTION. TEAMS ARE PROMOTED TO NEXT ROUND BASED ON CORRECT AND QUICKANSWERING. \n
ROUND 2:  SELECTED TEAMS HAVE TO MAKE A CIRCUIT WITH THE HELP OF GIVEN COMPLEX CIRCUIT DIAGRAM. THEY HAVE TO REDUCE IT TO SIMPLER FORM AND MAKE THE RESULTING CIRCUIT. THE GIVEN CIRCUIT DIAGRAM WILL BE A BLEND OF CIRCUIT THAT PARTICIPANTS COME ACROSS DAY TO DAY LIFE. \n
ROUND 3: QUIZ ON BASIC ELECTRONICS WILL BE CONDUCTED. TEAM WITH MORE POINTS WILL TURN OUT TO BE THE WINNER. \n
    </string>

    <string name="electrabuzz_rules">1.EACH TEAM IS OF 4-5 PEOPLE.\n
2. IN FIRST ROUND, ANSWER HAS TO BE WRITTEN ON QUESTION PAPER ALSO AND THE RESPECTIVE COMPONENT SHOULD BE DROPPED IN TEAM’S DROP BOX.\n
3.IN SECOND ROUND, SIMPLIFIED CIRCUIT HAS TO BE DRAWN ON THE QUESTION PAPER.\n
4.IN THIRD ROUND, NEGATIVE POINTS ARE ALSO AWARDED TO THE WRONG ANSWERS.\n
5.  +3, -1 ,0 POINTS ARE AWARDED TO CORRECT, WRONG AND NO ANSWER RESPECTIVELY\n
    </string>

    <string name="electrabuzz_contact">SIRIGIREDDY DHANALAXMI  7780134173 \n
    PERUL JAIN : 7891167889 \n
    </string>
    <string name="about_concetto">CONCETTO is the annual techno-management festival of INDIAN INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY (INDIAN SCHOOL OF MINES) DHANBAD. It also refers to the independent body of students who organize this event along with many other social initiatives and outreach programs around the year. CONCETTO is known for hosting a variety of events that include competitions, exhibitions, guest lectures as well as workshops. CONCETTO is Eastern India’s Largest Technical fest organized by the student body of the college.

The word “Concetto” means an opinion, an idea that has the revolutionary potential to shake the technical world.

Started in 2012, with the aim of providing a platform for the Indian student community to develop and showcase their technical prowess, it has now grown into East India’s Largest Science and Technology Festival with the participation of thousands of students from hundreds of Technical Institutes all around the nation. The activities culminate in a grand three-day festival event in the IIT (ISM) campus which attracts people from all over the country, including students, academia, corporates, and the general public as well. CONCETTO is all set to have its 8th Edition from 26th to 28th October’18.

The 3 day Technical Fiesta of IIT (ISM) DHANBAD- “CONCETTO” is one of the largest Techno-Management Fests in Eastern India with a massive participation of more than 10000 participants from hundreds of different institutes and colleges, who stalk the grounds of IIT (ISM) to prove their technical expertise, encompassing a platform to shoot the “TECHNICAL ME” of everyone. Apart from the various Robotics and Coding events, Concetto calls all the budding Entrepreneurs to showcase their innovative business skills. At the same time, hone your skills by joining our workshops taken by the eminent personalities in the various fields of science</string>
    <string name="electrabuzz_time">ROUND 1: 1 HR. \n
    ROUND 2: 1 HR. \n
    ROUND 3: 1 HR. \n
    </string>


    <string name="leverthehuge_desc">THIS EVENT IS TO COMPLETELY TO BRING OUT THE ENGINEER WITHIN THE NEW SPRUNG STUDENTS.\n
        DO YOU HAVE THE ABILITY TO DESIGN THE BASIC LEVER? COME OUT AND SHOW OF YOUR SKILLS USING THE BASIC MATERIALS AROUND YOU.\n
        HOPE YOU LIFT THE WEIGHTS AND AS WELL LIFT THE PRIZE.\n
PARTICIPANTS ARE EXPECTED TO PREPARE A MODEL CONSISTING THE BASIC LEVER SYSTEM.\n
        USE YOUR BASIC PHYSICS TO LIFT THE LOAD GIVEN BY US ON THE SPOT.\n
        EVENT ORGANISERS WILL ALWAYS BE AVAILABLE TO ASSIST YOU DURING THE PREPARATION OF YOUR MODEL. DO CONTACT US FOR FURTHER DOUBTS.
    </string>

    <string name="leverthehuge_rules">	HEIGHT LIMIT OF MECHANISM :80cm\n
	LENGTH LIMIT OF MECHANISM:100cm\n
	WOOD MATERIAL TO BE USED ONLY.\n
	STRING LOOPING IS NOT ALLOWED.\n
	WEIGHTS WILL BE PROVIDED.\n
	PULLEYS LIMIT (IF USED): 3

      ->  1.	The distance/height lifted by the system- 30% POINTS\n
->2.	Maximum weight that can be lifted- 50% POINTS\n
->3.	Design of mechanism - 20% POINTS\n
    </string>

    <string name="leverthehuge_rewards_criteria">
        ->  1.	The distance/height lifted by the system- 30% POINTS\n
->2.	Maximum weight that can be lifted- 50% POINTS\n
->3.	Design of mechanism - 20% POINTS\n
    </string>

    <string name="leverthehuge_contact">   DEVASHISH BARIKO -> 9398889882\n
             GOWTHAM DVSS -> 9631510705\n
    </string>

    <string name="leverthehuge_time">3 Hours</string>


    <string name="modelthecaravel_task">Participating teams have to design a boat which will be tested on
different parameters during the competition</string>

    <string name="modelthecaravel_desc"><b>TASK</b>\n
        Participating teams have to design a boat which will be tested on
different parameters during the competition\n\n
        The entire event is only to exhibit the creativity and designing of the
participants.\n
Each participating team has to design a boat which can be made up of
materials like plastic, metal, empty cans, thermocol, cardboard,glass,
etc.\n
        This boat will run using motors which will be powered by DC
batteries.\n
Each team have to use minimum one motor while the maximum limit
can be 4.
    </string>


    <string name="modelthecaravel_rules">Participating teams must consists of atleast two members while the
        max. Limit can go upto 4. \n
        Each team will be awarded total marks out of 100,in these 100 marks
        we will consider the design of boat, no. of motors used, technical
        knowledge of team and also two rounds will be conducted to test their
        models practically(i.e. race). \n
    </string>


    <string name="modelthecaravel_winning_criteria">The winners will be decided on the basis of total marks gained by
each team out of 100.</string>

    <string name="modelthecaravel_prizes">1st prize-2500/- \n
2nd prize-1500/- \n
3rd prize-1000/- \n
    </string>

    <string name="modelthecaravel_contact">Sagar Rathor-17JE003356 Contact no.-7877529922 \n
Pankaj Kumar-17JE002806 Contact no.-8207691824 \n
    </string>


    <string name="truss_desc">Ever thought how the bridges and buildings across the world are so stable and balanced? How a simple structure is enough to carry the heaviest load? Not yet!! Well! its never too late.\n
Experience the world of construction in a miniature form by constructing a Truss Bridge. Truss Bridge is the type of bridge whose main element is a truss, which is a structure of connected elements that form triangular units.\n
        Truss is used because it is very rigid structure and it transfers the load from single point to much wider area and are economic to construct. But the closed bridges provide obstacle for better transportation along the river.\n
        To overcome this hurdle, the new concept called HYDRAULIC ASSISTED BRIDGE (HAB) is used that provides the feasible transportation.\n
Participants are required to build a Hydraulic Assisted truss bridge with the following material\n\n
1.	100 popsicle sticks \n 2. Fevicol\n 3. Syringe\n 4. Narrow hose pipe Note: - All the materials will be provided by event organizers.\n\n

</string>

    <string name="truss_guidelines">
        ->50% points — Efficiency of the bridge. (Weight of load/Weight of bridge)\n
->20% points — The gap between the base of truss. (If it is 25cm= full marks will be awarded	otherwise points
->will be rewarded accordingly)\n
->20% points — Elevation of the bridge from the horizon (From the top of the base). If it is 15cm+	full marks will be\n
->awarded otherwise points will be rewarded accordingly.\n
->10% points — Creative design and peculiarity.

</string>

    <string name="truss_rules">•	The Bridge should be in the specified dimensions limit. Minimum height of the closed bridge — 15 cm. Maximum length — 45 cm.
Minimum gap between the base of the bridge —10 cm Maximum width — 10 cm\n
•	The sticks can be altered physically by notching or cutting at any angle\n
•	The overlapping of one stick over the other should not exceed 20%. (DOUBLING OF STICKS IS NOT PERMITTED)\n
•	No GLUE other than the one provided (Fevicol) must be used.\n
•	Penalties --\n
1.	Dimensional specifications are not met — Maximum of 10% Penalty per specification (of the total score) as per rules violation.\n
2.	Use of any other material other than the ones provided — DISQUALIFIED/\n
        3.	If Syringe is taking load — DISQUALIFIED\n
4.	Use of superglues — DISQUALIFIED\n\n
        ->	<b>Team Size</b> — 4 Students\n
        ->	Entry Fee - 400\n


    </string>

    <string name="truss_contact">1-	Rohit kumar->8678877133\n
2-	Deepansh Deepak srivastav -> 9082140959\n
    </string>

    <string name="truss_time">Last Two Days</string>


    <string name="triathlon_intro">A Three day long event comprised of three stage to feel the zeal of participating in bidding, quizzing and unveil the enterpreneurship inside you to solve the problems faced by industries on day to day basis. \n
Stage 1- Bid-Vaganza \n

Participants will be provided fixed amount of virtual cash. Participants will bid on the buildings present in the IIT(ISM) campus that will be put on the auction. \n
Stage 2- Concee-quiz \n

Second round will be the general quiz. Stage 3- Caliber \n
Industrial problems will be provided to the participants and participants have to come up with a innovative solution to the Problem. \n
    </string>

    <string name="triathlon_rules">1- Participants will be sorted according to the credit value of building in their basket and ready cash in their hand after the completion of bidding. \n
2-	Their will be no elimination in the first round. \n

3-	Marks of stage1 and stage 2 will be sum up to sort the participants for stage3. 4-Final	winners will solely be decided on the basis of score of stage3. \n
    </string>

    <string name="triathlon_contact">1-Surya Kumar Samadhiya :-9304154418 \n
        2- Sahil :- 725592778 \n
    </string>

    <string name="triathlon_time">3 Days (150 minutes daily) </string>
    <string name="googleminerabout">
        The event is to know how fast the participants can Google search in limited time and get maximum answers. The participants will have multiple clue regarding the answer in the question itself. The questions will be on various topics.\n
        <b>TASK</b>\n
        To google about the question and find the right answer.\n

There's no right way to solve it, but there's only one right answer.



    </string>
    <string name="googleminerrules">
        ->	Participating team must consist of maximum 3 participants.\n
->	Mobile phone with internet connectivity is required to Google about questions and find the answer.

    </string>
    <string name="googleminerjudging">
        Team with highest marks will be winners. The marks will be based on:\n
->	Number of correct answers\n
->	Ideas and Thinking

    </string>
    <string name="googleminercontacts">
        Dhanit Guria -> 7004721451
        Maripuddi Vamshi -> 9121561571
    </string>
    <string name="frothabout">
        Froth floatation process is a process for selectively separating hydrophobic materials from hydrophilic. This is used in mineral processing, paper recycling and waste water treatment industries.\n
        <b>TASK:</b>\n
        To concentrate sulphide ore.\n
        This event is for to exhibit the designing ability of the participants. The participants should prepare the model which should be able to concentrate the ore given in the event. The ore may be sulphide ore or coal. \n




    </string>
    <string name="frothrules">
        There will be a team of maximum 3 participants.\n
        <b>REQUIREMENTS:</b>\n
1.	Chemicals (Provided by Organisers)\n
2.	Air Blower\n
3.	A Bowl

    </string>
    <string name="frothjudging">
        The winners will be the top 3 teams getting maximum points. The points will be based on\n
1.	How good the model look -20 Points\n
2.	Some innovative change-20 Points\n
3.	Amount of Froth obtained-30 Points\n
4.	A quiz on Froth Floatation-30 Points

    </string>
    <string name="frothcontacts">
        mithun kr yadav - 9065090837\n
        sumit choudhary - 8486146283
    </string>
    <string name="borntowanderabout">
        <b>TASK</b>:-\n
Wander fast and get the ANSWERS asked.\n
<b>DESCRIPTION:-</b>\n\n
*You will be given clues to find how to wander.\n
* Then find things which were mentioned in the slip and do carry them with you.\n
*submit them at the first place, at the end.\n

    </string>
    <string name="bornrules">
        1. There will be a team of maximum of three participants\n
2. Where there is a requirement to take a selfie all the team members must be present in the selfie\n
3. Everything is with in campus do not go outside the campus.
REWARD CRITERIA
    </string>
    <string name="flashabout">
        Here is the mission for you. The robot you make has to play a crucial role. The mission is to carry THE SECRET CODES from CODE_SQUARE to DATA_RING. You do not have much time. The clock is ticking fast. Should you choose to accept it?\n

        <b>PROBLEM STATEMENT</b>\n
 Teams have to build an autonomous bot that can follow a white line over a coloured surface to move between the different zones and perform the required tasks.\nThe arena will consist of the Starting Zone (SZ), Code Square (CS), Data Ring (DR) and timers T1 and T2.\n The bot will start from the SZ and follow the thick white path. It will reach the CS where it has to identify a set of operators (+, -, x, %) and operands (a, b, c), where a, b, c are small integers encoded using combinations of LEDs.\n The mapping of operators and operands to LEDs of CS are shown clearly in table 1. The bot has to calculate that arithmetic expression. Once it has done its work at CS, it has to move to DR, where it shall transmit of evaluated result(magnitude only) of expression using its binary equivalent with the help of a set of 5-LEDs (An ON LED will represent ‘1’ and an OFF LED will represent ‘0’).\n\n
        <b>Guidelines and Suggestions</b>
1)	Along with an Arduino board, make use of light detecting sensors like photo-diode, light-dependent resistor (LDR), photo-transistors, LEDs.\n
2)	Strictly follow the dimensions of CODE_SQUARE and place your sensors accordingly to get accurate readings and prevent misalignments.\n
3)	The codes given by CODE_SQUARE will change on the spot i.e. they will be different for different bots. Thus, the bot should be programmed to adapt according to every possible code given.
    </string>
    <string name="flashtasks">
        <b>Level 1:</b>
The first task will check the bot’s locomotion capabilities. The bot will have to travel path by following the thick white line. The bots who are successfully able to do this will qualify this stage.
Bot should complete this level without any human intervention. In case of any human intervention the respective penalties will be awarded.
Maximum time limit: 10 minutes.\n
Points awarded: \n\n
•	50 points on completion of level.\n
•	-5 for each human intervention.\n

<b>Level 2:</b>
The Second level is where the real challenge begins. The bot will start from SZ and travel the path to reach CS. Now according to table 1, decode the code given through LED’s and convert it into a meaningful arithmetic expression and then calculate the value and store that value as it will be used later. Also, initially all the 4 LED’s will be ON for the bot to properly align itself to take those readings. Make sure that after the bot has stopped on CS it signals in the form of an external LED after which the code will be exposed (refer note 1). After taking the readings from CS the bot will move to DR where it will display the calculated output number in the form of binary which is advised to be done with the help of 5-LEDs placed in a line (array) on the bot.
Maximum time limit: 15 minutes.\n
Points awarded:\n\n
•	20 points for stopping at CS.\n
•	20 points for successfully collecting data from CS.\n
•	10 points for crossing to path break.\n
•	15 points for successfully crossing ‘L’ junction.\n
•	70 points for displaying correct answer at DR.\n
•	-5 points for touch for each physical contact.\n
        <b>Note1:</b>
Initially all the LEDs of CS will be on, in order to help the bot properly align. The bot must signal only after it has properly aligned.\n

<b>Tie-breaker Level:</b>\n\n
This level will be open only for those team whose points are coincident and in top three scores. Quantitative tie-breaking strategies will be employed. The strategies will be disclosed on the spot.\n


    </string>
    <string name="flashrules">
        1)	Only one bot per team is allowed.\n
2)	A team can have a maximum of 4 members.\n
3)	Sharing or exchanging of bots within teams is not allowed.\n
4)	Explicit physical contact with the bot during the course of the event is not allowed without the organizer’s permission. Doing so can lead to a penalty or even disqualification.\n
5)	In case the bot leaves the defined track, the respective team will have to restart from the Starting Zone.\n
6)	Each participant has to bring his/her Identity Proof to be checked by the organizers at the time of the event.



    </string>
    <string name="flashcontacts">
        Nikhitha ->	8919340777\n
Pradyumna Gupta ->	7023086751\n
        Yash Raj ->	7488420275\n


    </string>
    <string name="flashbot">
        1)	 The size of the bot should not be more than 17x17x10 (cm). Care should be taken such that it fits in the arena properly.\n
2)	 Use of internal combustion engines in the bot is not allowed.\n
3)	 The bot can have its own power source. An external Power source of 220 Volts AC will be provided if needed. However, teams are suggested to confine the power source within the bot. \n
4)	 Teams are permitted to implement their own choice of sensors.\n
5)	 Teams are allowed to use readymade microcontrollers, an array of LDR, IR or any other sensor as per their requirement.\n
6)	Bots with power source confined within the bot (i.e. not using an adapter to power the bot) will be rewarded bonus points\n
7)	 Teams are not allowed to use any readymade Lego kits or any such assemblies.\n
8)	 Any type of violation can result to disqualification.

    </string>
    <string name="obstacleabout">
        The participant shall hereafter be referred to as the player and their robot, the bot.\n
In this event the player is supposed to complete a course littered with obstacles, the player who finishes in the least amount of score wins the event. The obstacles can be either active or passive; active – they can deliberately delay the bot or passive – they can make it harder to continue.\n
The bot must not harm or otherwise deliberately sabotage the Arena. They must adhere to the following rules while participating in the event.\n

    </string>
    <string name="obstaclespecs">
        •	It must be a manually controlled bot, i.e. there must be a way for the player to control the movements of the bot. It can have some automatic features but the decision to toggle those features should lie with the player.
•	Extra points will be awarded to wireless bots.\n
•	The dimensions of the bot must be less than 20 centimetres by 18 centimetres (length by width) and it must less than 20 centimetres.\n
•	The maximum permissible weight for the bot is 2.5 kilograms.\n
•	It must use a DC motor.\n
•	An adapter will be present beside the arena to resolve issues of length of wire and faulty equipment. The player must use the provided adapter which will be of 12V – 2A.\n
•	The bot must complete the entire course. Shortcuts are a strict no-no.\n\n

In case of any discrepancies in the rules, the view of the presiding judge over the event shall be final and binding. Decisions regarding exceptional cases shall also lie in the hands of the presiding judge.
 


    </string>
    <string name="obstarules">
        •	The players must not enter the arena unless given permission by the presiding judge.\n
•	The player must not directly or indirectly nudge or otherwise touch the bot once the race has started without prior permission of the presiding judge.\n
•	The bot shall only be controlled by one person which cannot be changed once the race has started. The team leader shall intimate identity of the controller to the presiding judge.\n
•	In case of any violation of rules, the team shall be instantly disqualified.

    </string>
    <string name="obstajudging">
        •	The players must not enter the arena unless given permission by the presiding judge.\n
•	The player must not directly or indirectly nudge or otherwise touch the bot once the race has started without prior permission of the presiding judge.\n
•	The bot shall only be controlled by one person which cannot be changed once the race has started. The team leader shall intimate identity of the controller to the presiding judge.\n
•	In case of any violation of rules, the team shall be instantly disqualified.

    </string>
    <string name="obstacontacts">
        •	Prakhar Kumar ->+91-9559801909\n
•	Harsh Vardhan ->+91-9608722879\n
•	Eric John -> +91-9570093144

    </string>
    <string name="roboelig">
        <b>Eligibility</b> \n   Team from any recognized engineering college are eligible to participate.\n
        <b>Team Specification:</b> Any team consisting of maximum 4 members can participate.\n
        <b>Team Name</b> : Every team must have an appropriate name which must be unique. Team's name won’t be change once submitted.\n
        <b>Team Representative:</b> Each team must specify their Team Representative (Leader) at the time of registration on the website or app.\n\n
All important communications between Concetto (Robowars) and the registered
teams will be done through their Team Representative.
The Team Representatives must submit valid contact details (Mobile no., email ID etc.) at the time of registration.

    </string>
    <string name="robojudging">
        •	Points will be given on the basis of aggression and damage.\n
	Aggression – Points on aggression will be awarded on the basis of frequency, boldness and effectiveness of attacks attempted by the robot against its opponent.\n
	Damage – Points on damage will be awarded if the robot reduces the functionality, effectiveness or defensibility of an opponent either directly or indirectly. Win the game by immobilizing your opponent’s bot.\n
	Any foul play by any of the teams would result in deduction of score.\n


<b>Certification</b>
•	Certificates of Participation will be given to all the participating teams.\n
•	Certificate of appreciation and prizes will be given to all the winners.\n


    </string>
    <string name="roborules">
        <b>General Rules</b>
•	There will be two rounds, 10 minutes each.\n
•	In no case should the arena be damaged by any robot.\n

<b> Round 1 </b>\n
•	Opponents shall be selected on lottery basis.\n
•	 seconds will be given to each team before the start of each round to set
their bot. Any team that is not ready at the time specified will be disqualified.\n
•	If no robot is immobilized within the time limit then winner will be judged on the basis of point scored.\n\n
<b>Round 2</b>\n
•	Best 6 scorers will be selected for next round of Battle where they will compete against each other.\n
•	Final winners will be decided on the basis of cumulative points for both the rounds.\n

•	Violation of any of the above rules or any misconduct will lead to disqualification.\n\n

        <b>Note:</b>\n- The organizers reserve the rights to change, any or all of the above rules as they deem fit. Decision of organizers will be final and binding on all.\n\n
        <b>Safety	Rules</b>\n
It is expected that competitors stay within the rules.\n
•	Special care should be taken to protect the batteries and pneumatics on the Bot.\n
•	Proper activation and deactivation of robots is important. Robots must only be activated in the arena, testing areas, or with expressed consent of the event coordinators.\n
•	All weapons must have a safety cover on any sharp or sharpen edges.\n
•	All participants build and operate robots at their own risk.\n
Please take care to not hurt yourself or others when building, testing and competing. Any kind of activity which may cause damage to the surroundings during the stay of the teams in the competition area should not be carried out without the consent of organizers. Not following this rule may result in disqualification.\n
•	Once the robots have entered into the arena, no team member can enter into the arena at any point of time.

    </string>
    <string name="robospecs">
        <b>Net Dimensions and Fabrications</b>\n
•	The Main body of bot should fit into a box of 1’6’’x1’6’’x1’6’’ (lxbxh),
i.e. 45x45x45 cm.\n
The external device used to control the machine or any external tank is not
included in the size constraint.\n
•	The machine should not exceed 30kg of weight for robot having pneumatic source/tank and 25kg for wired robot on board.\n
•	In case of wireless robot if the battery is on-board then the weight will be taken as 0.80 x Actual Weight.\n

        <b>Power Sources</b>
•	The machine can be powered electrically only.\n
•	Each team must prepare its own power sources. The teams have to bring their
own battery eliminators/adaptor.\n
•	Use of DC motor is mandatory, the voltage difference between any two points in
the machine should not be more than 36V DC at any point of time.\n

        <b>Safety is first priority.</b>
•	All connections should be made safe to prevent short circuits and battery fires. Any unsafe circuitry may result in disqualification.\n
•	Use of damaged, non-leak proof batteries may lead to disqualification.\n
•	Change of battery will not be allowed during the match unless timeout is taken by
either of the team.\n
•	It is suggested to have extra batteries ready and charged.\n
•	No provision will be provided for charging of batteries around the arena.

<b>Mobility</b>
•	Freedom of mobility may include:\n
	Rolling (wheels, tracks or the whole robot).\n
	Walking (linear actuated legs with no rolling).\n
•	Any other method of mobility which leads the robot to lose contact with the ground is not allowed.\n
        <b>Robot Control Requirements</b>
•	Extra marks will be awarded to Wireless Robots.\n
a>You can use the external power supply to power your robot.\n
•	The wires which you may use to supply the power to your robot (properly protected and insulated), which will be coming out of the robot should be bundled as a single unit.\n
•	The wire should be sufficiently long so as to remain slack at all time during the war, it is recommended to attach a pipe to bot in vertical direction through which wires come out.\n
•	For wireless remote controls, it is recommended that the remote should have at least two frequency operations to prevent interference with other team.\n\n


<b>Weapon Systems</b>\n
•	Robots can have any kind of cutters, flippers, saws, lifting devices, spinning hammers etc. as weapons with following exceptions and limitations:\n
	Any kind of inflammable liquid / liquid projectiles.\n
	Smoke or dust based weapons.\n
	Any kind of explosive or intentionally ignited solid or potentially ignitable solid.\n
	Nets, tape, glue, or any other entanglement device.\n
	High power magnets or electromagnets\n
	Radio Jamming, Tasers, Tesla coils, or any other high-voltage device.\n
•	Spinning weapons which do not come in contact with the arena at any point of
time are allowed.\n

    </string>
    <string name="robocontacts">
        •	Ayan   Prakash -> 918809075447
•	Jalaj -> +918878209475
•	Prince Kunal -> +919386667625
•	Shantanu -> +919424697088

    </string>
    <string name="sympabout">
        Having technical knowledge is no more an auxiliary trait, it has become our necessity. Technical stuff is not about mugging, it also demands for your awareness towards technical world of inventions and discussions. Get a chance to express yourself and share your knowledge with others. If you see yourself as a techno-freak, it’s time to explore your technical and presentation skills in Symposium.\n\n
<b>TOPICS –</b>\n\n
• Scope of Machine learning in Geophysics\n
• Seismology of Himalayan arc and Burmese arc Region\n
• Crustal study of Mars (Comparative study with Earth)\n
• Geophysical Methods for mineral exploration • Automatic detection of seismic events in urban areas\n
• Unconventional Reservoirs- Hydrates, Shale gas, CBM etc.(any one)\n
• Vertical Seismic Profiling (VSP)\n
• Groundwater Exploration using Geo electric Sounding\n
• Marine Geophysics\n
• Airborne Survey and Technicalities
    </string>
    <string name="symprules">
        1. State the principle objectives, the scope of the investigation or the reason for addressing the topic (the “what” and “why”). This would include your thesis statement.\n
2. Describe very briefly the methodology employed or the approach to the problem or topic (the “how” or “where”).\n
3. Summarize the results that were found. If some studies had similar findings, then you don’t need to elaborate on each study.\n
4. State the principal conclusions. What do the results of your studies suggest?\n\n
The abstract should not exceed 200 words and should be fully self-contained; that is, it must make sense to someone not familiar with the topic. It should be typed as a single paragraph and must contain complete sentences with correct grammar and spelling. The abstract should
not give information or conclusions that are not in the paper or presentation. It should not contain bibliographic information, figures or references. Omit abbreviations and acronyms.\n
<b>Submit your abstract on:</b> \n
        agpism2018@gmail.com\n
<b>Last Date for abstract submission:</b>\n
        25th October 2018\n
<b>Time Limit for Presentation</b>:\n
        8 min Presentation and 2 min Q/A
    </string>
    <string name="symjudge">
        <b>• Content:</b>/n
        30 points
<b>• Presentation:</b> \n
        20 points
        <b>• Q/A:</b>\n
        10 points\n
• 2 marks will be deducted for each minute beyond the time limit
    </string>
    <string name="symcontacts">
        Shubham Kumar -> 7004016692
    </string>
    <string name="chemcarabout">

The aim of the competition is to provide students with an opportunity to design and
construct a small chemically powered car and test the ability of participants to safely
control and harness the energy of a chemical reaction by initiating the car and allowing
it to traverse a fixed distance carrying a certain load.\n\n
        A)   <b>ROUND 1</b>\n

➣ Each Team will be allowed to give one run to test their model. In this run, the model would
     be checked whether it emits harmful chemicals (concentrated acid, poisonous gases,
     etc.),  your team would be eliminated if chemicals are hazardous and harmful for the
     Surroundings.\n

➣The model should cover a minimum distance of 5m. If they are unable to do so, their
    teams would be disqualified.\n

B) <b>ROUND 2</b>\n

➣The car is expected to carry a specified payload (most probably water) of 500
    grams(Note: payload will be provided at the competition site.)\n
➣The car must have a chamber for the container in which load will be placed.\n
➣One of the organiser from our team will measure the payload and it would be
    given to you to pour it into your container.

C)  <b>ROUND 3</b>\n

The final qualifications for stage 3 would entirely be dependent on stage 2 winners.The teams will be asked to give a brief overview (lasting 4 minutes) about their model to the judges, followed by viva by the judges.. The Teams will be questioned, and based on their understanding and the performance of the model they will be graded.


    </string>
    <string name="chemcarjud">
        The criteria for judging will be as following:\n\n

➣  Round 1: Trial runs (Weightage 30%).\n
➣  Round 2: Payload (Weightage 50%).\n
➣  Round 3: Presentation Round (Weightage 20%)\n\n

The judging for all rounds will be done by the judges of the competition who shall also decide upon disqualification and penalisation in cases of breaching of rules.

    </string>
    <string name="chemcarcont">
        ROHIT AGRAWAL ->7462876817


    </string>

    <string name="chemcarrules">
        ➣ Each team can consist of at most 4 members. Multiple teams from the same institution
    are allowed, provided their abstracts and models are not the same.\n
    ➣Teams must strictly adhere to the given deadlines, failing to do so will lead to heavy
    penalisation in points or disqualification.\n
    ➣Transportation of chemicals to the competition venue is strictly the responsibility of the
    Team. You are also responsible for arranging disposal of chemical wastes generated by
    your model.(Note:Facility for disposal will be provided at the competition site)\n
    ➣Your Chem-E-Car model should be built based on the final abstract submitted.\n
    ➣The decision of the judges or event coordinators will be considered final and no further
    arguments would be entertained.\n


    </string>
    <string name="carabout">
Each team can consist of at most 4 members and min 2 members\n\n<b>problem statement</b>\n
    Your team is given a list of reactions which is required to completed. To complete
It, your team require certain chemicals. At the starting you’ve certain chemical, but the twist is they are insufficient to complete any one of reaction.\n\n

    <b>Solution</b>\n
You’ve to trade your chemicals with other teams. So, every team has to decide which chemicals to sold, and bought. Now, trading would be in form of bidding, and would be through bank (organizers) only.\n
Winner will be decided on the basis of maximum no. of reactions completed at the end of event.

    </string>
    <string name="carjud">
        <b>How to play</b>
Every team will be given a ledger, on which they’ve to register every trade they’ve made during each round of bidding.\n

Ex. \n




Compound
Round 1 Round 2 Round 3
A  B  C
+2 -  -\n
-1 +3 -\n
-  +4 -\n
        Here +2 represent buying, while -1 represents selling.\n\n


<b>Pricing Dynamics:</b>\n
Initially certain value would given by bank to every compound. As rounds we’ll be progress prices will change based on the rule of demand and supply. Compounds higher in demand, will have higher price, and vice versa for compounds low in demand.\n

Ex.\n
Let every chemical have an intial value of $100/mol.\n
Take Team 1, it has 2 moles of compound B.\n
And it bids chemical A $100/mol, for 0.5 mol.\n
Hence, Team 1 has to exchange 1mol of B\n
For Bank,\n
Then, before bidding\n
        Compound A        Compound B\n
Price(mol)    $100 (1)        $100 (1)\n

After bidding,\n\n
        Compound A        Compound B\n
Price(mol)    $200(0.5)        $100(2)\n
    =$400(1)        = $50\n



    </string>
    <string name="carcon">
        Rishabh Verma -> 9977991841\n

      .Prashant Choudhary ->7091025596

    </string>
    <string name="carrules">
        Each round will cover all chemical compounds once.\n
There is no limitation on teams regarding number of bids.\n
There will be only specific amount of chemical placed for bidding by bank, also if there is less than 0.5 mol available of a given compound, then it’ll not be bid unless it is sold to bank in that round.\n\n
        <b>Bidding Rules:</b>\n
Any wrong bidding, i.e. placing bid more than in account, will result in disqualification.\n
Any illegal manipulation of ledger result in disqualification\n
No team can cancel bid once placed.\n\n

5.If any bid is found wrong, then next highest bidder is taken, and so on.\n
6.Only one member of team is allowed to place the bid, rest can discuss among.

    </string>
    <string name="electroabout">
The event consists of three rounds:
<b>ROUND 1:-</b> \n
        (Written Exam) It consists of a pen and paper based exam with questions on solving electrical circuits containing resistors, capacitors, inductors etc. and some aptitude questions.\n
<b>ROUND 2:</b>\n -(Dumb Charades) The Intermediate round which tests your ability to relate technical words to your daily life aspects as soon as possible, as only 2 minutes are given to each team. One member from each team will be given some technical word which he has to explain to his partner without uttering a single word.\n
        <b>ROUND 3:</b> \n-(Interview) This round will test your group knowledge through personal interview.
    </string>
    <string name="electrorules">
        <b>ROUND 1</b>\n
        • Correct answer will be awarded with 4 marks, wrong answer will be result in -1 mark and in case of no attempt, Zero marks will be deduced.\n
• The team which qualify the exam above cut-off below threshold limit will be continue in the next Round.\n\n
        <b>ROUND 2
        </b>\n
        • No mode of communication will be allowed except hand gestures.\n
• Time limit for each team is 2 minutes.\n
• No electronic gadgets for communication will be permitted.\n\n
        <b>ROUND 3</b>\n
        RULES:- • The group performs well will be awarded marks according to judges.\n\n
        • Registration fee is ZERO\n
• Team consists maximum of 4 members and minimum 3.\n
• Use of mobile phones and cheating leads to disqualification of team.\n
• Decision of judges is final.
    </string>
    <string name="electrochcon">
        Bharadwaj Donthula - (9392427427)\n
Gouni sandeep kumar - (8247554468)

    </string>
    <string name="electrchjud">
        Judgement depends on the final score made by the team by completion of third round and it also depends on how much they understood observations and experimenting circuits.
    </string>
    <string name="teslabaout">
        The event consists of two rounds:-\n\n
<b>ROUND 1:-</b>\n
Here participants will be provided circuit elements. By using them participants have to make the tesla
circuit. According to their design and conceptual understanding will help them to qualify for next round.\n\n

<b>ROUND 2:-</b>\n
Here each team member will have to give a pen paper based Quiz .After that there will be a
personal interview related to the wireless technology.

    </string>
    <string name="teslarule">
        <b>
            ROUND 1
        </b>\N
        1. The CFL provided must glow properly.\n
2. Design of slayer circuit.\n
3. Conceptual understanding (In case of tie).\n
Only 10 teams will qualify for 2nd round based on the time of completion of circuit and glowing of
bulb.\n\n

<b>ROUND 2:-</b>\n
        1. Marks will be given according to the answer given by the team members\n\n
        <b>GENERAL RULES:-</b>\n
1. NO registration fees.\n
2. Money will be taken for circuit elements which teams can take with them after the event.\n
3. Team must of 3 members only.\n
4. Use of mobile phones or other gadgets are not allowed.\n
5. Decision of judges will be final.
    </string>
    <string name="teslajud">
        Judgement depends on the final score made by the team by completion of second round and it
also depends on how much they understood by observations and experimenting circuits
    </string>
    <string name="tescon">
        Tarun kumar ->(8507359111)
    </string>
    <string name="bafabout">
        <b>Round 1:</b>\n
Teams consisting of 3 to 4 members will compete with each other on the basis of their
knowledge of elementary earth sciences. A problem sheet will be provided to each team.\n\n
<b>Round 1:</b>\n
Teams selected from round 1 will have an interactive pictionary round. With the blend of
Science, this round will be full of fun and something to look forward to.\n\n
<b>Round 2B:</b>
This round will be a treasure hunt. To add to the twist, this will be an indoor treasure hunt. This
is where things really get interesting.\n\n
<b>Round 3:</b>\n
This round is a surprise round. This round will check how well-versed one is with the innovations
and technologies of the present day. Applying these techs in any field to provide an effective
solution is what a technophile should look forward to. This said, this round seeks an innovative
mind.
    </string>
    <string name="bafrules">
        Teams must have at least 3 members.\n
● The number of teams selected from round 1 will depend upon the participation.\n
● The cumulative score of rounds 2A and 2B will be assessed for qualification to the third
round.\n
● Each of the 5 teams selected for round 3 will get cash prizes based to their final score.\n

    </string>
    <string name="bafcon">
        Anuj Gupta
        Pushpendra Singh Deora
    </string>
    <string name="aquaabout">
        <b>TASK:</b> \n
To shift objects from one place to other using hydraulic arm.\n
<b>DESCRIPTION:</b>\n
The event is focused on lifting and moving of object with the help of hydraulic arm. The arm moves with the movement of water when you push the plunger on a syringe, water is forced from one syringe into another which do some mechanical movement to lift the object. The process illustrates aspects of fluid pressure, force, mechanical work, and biomechanics.\n\n
<b>REQUIREMENTS:</b>\n
•	Syringes, Hard board, wood, rubber bands.

    </string>
    <string name="aquarules">
        •	Maximum of 3 people are allowed in a team.\n
•	The fluid inside the syringes should be water.\n
•	Weight limit/ and other dimensions will be given\n.
•	Use of batteries, Electric motors, springs, compressors and pressurized cylinders are prohibited.\n
•	In case of any discrepancy, the decision of the judges shall be treated as final and binding on all.

    </string>
    <string name="aquajud">
        Winner will be the one getting maximum points. The points will be based on the following criteria:\n
•	Time taken for completion of given task.\n
•	Design of the hydraulic arm.\n
•	Lifting mechanisms.

    </string>CONCETTO is the annual techno-management festival of INDIAN INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY (INDIAN SCHOOL OF MINES) DHANBAD. It also refers to the independent body of students who organize this event along with many other social initiatives and outreach programs around the year. CONCETTO is known for hosting a variety of events that include competitions, exhibitions, guest lectures as well as workshops. CONCETTO is Eastern India’s Largest Technical fest organized by the student body of the college.

The word “Concetto” means an opinion, an idea that has the revolutionary potential to shake the technical world.

Started in 2012, with the aim of providing a platform for the Indian student community to develop and showcase their technical prowess, it has now grown into East India’s Largest Science and Technology Festival with the participation of thousands of students from hundreds of Technical Institutes all around the nation. The activities culminate in a grand three-day festival event in the IIT (ISM) campus which attracts people from all over the country, including students, academia, corporates, and the general public as well. CONCETTO is all set to have its 8th Edition from 26th to 28th October’18.

The 3 day Technical Fiesta of IIT (ISM) DHANBAD- “CONCETTO” is one of the largest Techno-Management Fests in Eastern India with a massive participation of more than 10000 participants from hundreds of different institutes and colleges, who stalk the grounds of IIT (ISM) to prove their technical expertise, encompassing a platform to shoot the “TECHNICAL ME” of everyone. Apart from the various Robotics and Coding events, Concetto calls all the budding Entrepreneurs to showcase their innovative business skills. At the same time, hone your skills by joining our workshops taken by the eminent personalities in the various fields of science
    <string name="thriiiabout">
        The task of this is as simple as can be. You are required to construct a framework which can adequately support the equipments. Drill through the obstructions efficiently to claim your prize. Sounds daunting, doesn\'t it! Well there\'s not much to worry about as we have a Workshop designed specifically to acquaint you with a vivid description of the intricacies involved.\n
<b>REQUIREMENT:</b>
➢ Things that will be provided in the kit.\n
• 3 Motors.\n
• Nut-Bolt sets.\n
• Plywood (1.5 sq. ft).\n
• 2 DPDT switches.\n
• Wire (1m).\n
• Slider.\n
• Connector.\n
➢ Drill chuck and the drill pipes will be provided at the time of event.\n

    </string>
<string name="thrillrules">
    TEAM:
    • Team must consist of 3 to 5 members.
    • Participation fee will be Rs 500 per team.
    MODEL:
    • Maximum height of the derrick is 45 cm.
    • The base area should not exceed 18*18 cm2.
    • No other motor should be used other than the one provided in the kit.
    • Use of iron, steel etc. is not allowed to design the derrick, only wooden framework is permitted.
    TIME LIMIT:
    • Maximum time limit to drill the composition is 30 minutes.
    • Minimum performing time is 6 minutes.
</string><string name="thrilljudging">Judging criterion includes a distribution of 100 points.\n
    • 60 POINTS for the length of drilled composition. (1 cm =1 point)\n
    • 20 POINTS for stability &amp; design of the Derrick.\n
    • 20 POINTS - Time {2/3 of the time remaining at the time of quitting}\n
    The one securing maximum number of points will be the winner. In case of a tie, time will be the judging criterion.</string>
    <string name="thrillcon">
        kshitij goyal -> 9425725040
    </string>
<string name="bfftabt">
    Do you have what it takes to be the top gun? Inviting all the analytic minds to fight it out for the top prize in Buffet Money, Concetto’s Virtual Stock Trading game. Buy, Sell and Trade in this intense three-day challenge and get a feel of the real market as you bid for real prices against real players. Engulf yourself in the nail-biting market swings as you would soon find out that money is the only thing virtual here. Rewards worth Rs. XXXX up for grabs. May the odds be ever in your favour
</string>
    <string name="bfftrules">
        1. Each team begins the simulation with $100,000 in cash.\n
2. It does not permit buying stocks that trade below $5 per share. Such orders will be rejected.\n
3. Sell transactions for existing long positions will be accepted, even if the price is less than $5.00 per share.\n
4. The Game is run Friday through sunday. You can trade on any day, the participating stock markets are open.\n
5. Trades entered after close of market (4:00p.m. Eastern Time) will be priced at next trading day\'s closing price.\n
6. To be eligible for final ranking the participant should make atleast 5 transactions on each day of the game;\n
7. Members do not have to liquidate their portfolios at the end of The Game. Winners will be determined on the basis of the equity in their portfolios at the end of the final transaction day.\n
8. A record of a participant's portfolio and transactions will be available daily. He/She will not receive a portfolio nor be listed in rankings until its initial transaction is entered successfully.\n
9. Stock and cash dividends and stock splits are automatically computed into your portfolio.\n
10. Participants of the end of day pricing game may delete pending transactions prior to market close.
    </string>
    <string name="bfftcon">
        Sahil Seli -> 8557891934\n
        Rishabh Baranwal -> 7355735863
    </string>
    <string name="unraabt">
        <b> Round 1  Domino </b>
The teams will fall so will the questions the goal of each team will be to solve questions as if they were in a relay race. The race can only be won with the combined effort of all the three members.
The questions of this round will be based on general mathematics and mental ability.\n\n
<b> Round 2- Divide and Conquer </b>
This round will be a complete surprise, teams shortlisted from the first round will be going to play this whizzing round.

    </string>
    <string name="unrarul">1. The team should comprise of exactly  3 members. \n
2. Carry a pen or pencil with you.\n
3. Use of Any electronic gadgets is strictly prohibited. If found guilty the team will be immediately disqualified.\n
4. Cheating in any form is a strict no -no. \n
5. If any team  indulges in any kind of misbehaviour or misconduct than the organisers have the right to immediately disqualify the team.\n
6.The decision of organisers in any case will be final and all must abide by it.
    </string>
    <string name="unravljud">
        <b>Round 1-</b>
1. Its a time based event.\n
2. All the members of a team will get different questions and they have to solve them separately.\n
3. The second member cannot solve his question until and unless the first member passes the answer of first question to him on a piece of paper and without any form of discussion.\n
Only the answer shall be passed on that piece of paper. Same rules are applicable for the third member.\n
4. Finally the third member has to submit his answer to the volunteers present. \n
5. Since the judgement will also be based upon time taken so members should try to be as quick as possible.\n\n

<b>Round 2-</b>\n
Rules for this round will be stated on the spot.
    </string>
    <string name="sparabt">
        •	<b>First Round</b>\n Would Consist of the questions Regarding the CEO, Higher management authorities, technology based and Company related questions where each team will be given a set of questions that they have to answer, Top 10 teams would be selected for next round.\n\n
•	 <b>Round 2</b> It will be conducted with the Help of Projector where Pictures will be displayed on the screen and the participants would be required to guess the right answer.\n\n
•	<b>Third Round</b> Would Consist of questions related to Latest Business changes and technical innovations.

    </string>
    <string name="sparrul">
        <b>Round 1- </b>\nThere will be 25-30 questions and time allotted will be approximately 30 minutes. Group members would discuss and mark the answer correctly. No Negative Marking.\n\n
<b>Round 2-</b>\n The Team Would Nominate 1 Member From The Group. The Logo/Symbols/Pictures would be Displayed and the member will have to guess the correct answer, time given would be 10 seconds each, team will Lose marks if the member Fails to answer. 2-3 such rounds will be conducted. Top 5 teams would go to the next round.\n\n
<b>Round 3- </b>Current Business and technological questions would be asked Individually to members of the teams for which 15 seconds will be provided. Each member of the team would get 1 question, and 1 bonus question for 1 team of 5 marks to make up.\n\n
In case of tie, tie breaker question would be asked.

    </string>
    <string name="sparcon">
        Deepti -> 7783024700\n
        Krishna Sudhakar Sonvane -> 9158464845
    </string>
    <string name="idpabt">
        The desire to create is one of the deepest yearnings of the human soul. The IDP - Industrial Design Problem will push the students to think beyond the conventional and to look at a problem in a different way and solve it in a limited amount of time. This event is going to be a simulator which will provide the competitors with real life environment for industrial challenges. The event is set to help the participants develop an industry sense. This is a quality every engineering aspirant needs to have regardless of the industry and/or the location they work in.\n\n
       <b>Event Structure</b> \n\n
1. The competition will be organized in two phases, both to be conducted at IIT (ISM) Dhanbad during Concetto'18.\n
2. The first round will have an aptitude test from which few teams will be selected for the second round.\n
3.For the second round a problem statement related to industry will be given, the solution to which has to be designed in a specified period of time.\n
4. Round 1 Aptitude Test will be 45min and Round 2 will be on next day of 1 hour period.


    </string>
    <string name="idpelig">
        <b>Eligibility</b>\n
The participant must be pursuing an UG/PG/Diploma program from a recognized institute. They may be asked to provide supporting documents so as to prove the above mentioned criteria.

    </string>
    <string name="idpcon">
             Satyam Kumar - 7352697063  \n
            Shivam Jaiswal - 7734842784

    </string>
    <string name="idprules">1. Each team can contain a maximum of 3 participants.\n
2. The decision of the judges will be final and binding.\n
3. Participants are requested to have their own stationaries.

    </string>
    <string name="laserabt">Laser tag is a tag game played with guns which fire infrared beams. Infrared-sensitive targets are commonly worn by each player and are sometimes integrated within the arena in which the game is played. There are flashing targets on your front, shoulders, back and on the sides and front of the gun. When you fire the gun, a laser beam is projected towards your target and when you are shot, your pack is deactivated for up to four seconds.A session lasts only 15 minutes and the rules insist there’s no running,climbing,crouching or crawling - so it’s not a game that burns a great number of calories. But it does engage all your senses, like a Native American tracker, as you try to assess where the next danger is coming from, and attempt to pick off your enemies.If there’s only two of you, staff will aim to integrate you with another group so it’s more fun. At the end, scores are displayed on monitors, and your individual hits are broken down.
If you’ve always secretly fancied yourself as an action hero trapped on a demonic spaceship facing an unknown enemy (and who hasn’t?), it’s got to be worth a try.

    </string>
    <string name="laserrules">
        A session lasts only 15 minutes and the rules insist there’s no running,climbing,crouching or crawling.
    </string>
    <string name="paperabt">
        Paper Dance is a competition among teams of two.The concept of the event is the pairs participating have to dance on a sheet of paper when the music plays and have to stop dancing when music stop. The sheet is folded into a half after every round and the pairs have to dance within the boundaries of the sheet.The sheet is folded till only a foot fits on the sheet and finally, the pair who can endure the diminishing sheet wins the game.
An A3 sheet of paper is spread on the ground for each team.

    </string>
    <string name="paperrules">
         In every round, each team has to dance on the sheet when the music starts.
The moment any team member has any part of the body touching the area outside the sheet is disqualified along with his or her partner.The sheet is folded into its half in every round till only one foot fits on it.
The team members have to continue dancing during the music is on. If they stops dancing in between to save.

    </string>
    <string name="paperjud">
         Judging will be based on compatibility between the team members and balance in their dance steps.

    </string>
    <string name="blindabt">
          A blind date is a social engagement game between two people who have not previously met, arranged randomly by organizers. The event is sponsored and endorsed by The Lemon Chilli Dhanbad. The game rolls down in steps of multiple rounds consist of various exciting and fun buzzing tasks. In each round participants will be shortlisted depending upon their performance in respective tasks.

    </string>
    <string name="blindtasks">
        This question has definitely striked into your mind that turns out to be butterflies in your stomach at the same time. But We’re not going to kill those cute bees. The tasks will be kept remain as surprise till the bang of moment. The Winners will get some fascinating prizes and goodies by the sponsors and the organizers.
    </string>
    <string name="memeabt">
        Meme Wars is an expression often referring to online rivalries in which opposing factions use internet memes to battle against one another or more generally as a clash of competing ideas.In case if you are unaware of this memolgic world here is all that a memer has to know :  meme is a virally-transmitted cultural symbol or social idea.
The majority of modern memes are captioned photos that are intended to be funny, often as a way to publicly ridicule human behavior. Other memes can be videos and verbal expressions. Some memes have heavier and more philosophical content.

    </string>
    <string name="memerul">
        Maximum of 3 entries are allowed for an individual.\n
Entries should not contain any content of violence, Sexuality, Religious or Political sentiments.

    </string>
    <string name="memejud">Each Haha react will get 5 points.\n Each like and other reactions contain 3 points.\n
    Winners will be decided by the final score including organizer’s decision(40%).

    </string>

</resources>
